{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299580570","data":{"timestamp":" 947299580570"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" cf730a55-1152-4437-9fe9-bfb4e6d3570a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299622795","data":{"timestamp":" 947299622794"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" cf730a55-1152-4437-9fe9-bfb4e6d3570a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299622950","data":{"timestamp":" 947299622950"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" cf730a55-1152-4437-9fe9-bfb4e6d3570a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nda..nda.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381539704","data":{"timestamp":" 947381539704"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" e4dfcebb-2531-4390-8cb2-f2162cfb053d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nda..nda.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nda_nda-go-twe"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nda"," userResponse":" nda"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nda..nda.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381545568","data":{"timestamp":" 947381545568"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" e4dfcebb-2531-4390-8cb2-f2162cfb053d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nda..nda.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nda_ba-mwu-nda"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nda"," userResponse":" nda"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nda..nda.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381550414","data":{"timestamp":" 947381550414"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" e4dfcebb-2531-4390-8cb2-f2162cfb053d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nda..nda.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nda_mte-mcho-nda"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nda"," userResponse":" nda"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nda..nda.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381555211","data":{"timestamp":" 947381555210"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" e4dfcebb-2531-4390-8cb2-f2162cfb053d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nda..nda.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nda_wi-nda-thi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nda"," userResponse":" thi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nda..nda.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381560865","data":{"timestamp":" 947381560865"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" e4dfcebb-2531-4390-8cb2-f2162cfb053d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nda..nda.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nda_wi-nda-thi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nda"," userResponse":" nda"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nda..nda.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381565908","data":{"timestamp":" 947381565908"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" e4dfcebb-2531-4390-8cb2-f2162cfb053d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nda..nda.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nda_ja-nda-wu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nda"," userResponse":" nda"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nda..nda.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381571490","data":{"timestamp":" 947381571489"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" e4dfcebb-2531-4390-8cb2-f2162cfb053d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nda..nda.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nda_li-nda-vye"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nda"," userResponse":" nda"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nda..nda.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381576168","data":{"timestamp":" 947381576168"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" e4dfcebb-2531-4390-8cb2-f2162cfb053d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nda..nda.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nda_mki-nda-di"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nda"," userResponse":" nda"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nda..nda.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381581568","data":{"timestamp":" 947381581568"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" e4dfcebb-2531-4390-8cb2-f2162cfb053d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nda..nda.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nda_ha-go-nda"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nda"," userResponse":" nda"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nda..nda.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381590502","data":{"timestamp":" 947381590502"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" e4dfcebb-2531-4390-8cb2-f2162cfb053d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nda..nda.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nda_mjo-nda-dha"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nda"," userResponse":" dha"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nda..nda.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381598738","data":{"timestamp":" 947381598738"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" e4dfcebb-2531-4390-8cb2-f2162cfb053d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nda..nda.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nda_mjo-nda-dha"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nda"," userResponse":" nda"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nda..nda.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381606398","data":{"timestamp":" 947381606398"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" e4dfcebb-2531-4390-8cb2-f2162cfb053d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nda..nda.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nda_vyu-po-nda"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nda"," userResponse":" nda"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nda..nda.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381612191","data":{"timestamp":" 947381612191"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" e4dfcebb-2531-4390-8cb2-f2162cfb053d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nda..nda.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_nda_vyu-po-nda"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381630254","data":{"timestamp":" 947381630254"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" e4dfcebb-2531-4390-8cb2-f2162cfb053d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nda..nda.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_nda_vyu-po-nda"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.nda..nda.noShow..22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381663044","data":{"timestamp":" 947381663043"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 5cf1b3e3-e746-4623-a958-00f96dd095c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.nda..nda.noShow..22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_nda_di_mpa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.nda..nda.noShow..22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381669664","data":{"timestamp":" 947381669664"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 5cf1b3e3-e746-4623-a958-00f96dd095c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.nda..nda.noShow..22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_le_chi_nda"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.nda..nda.noShow..22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381676325","data":{"timestamp":" 947381676325"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 5cf1b3e3-e746-4623-a958-00f96dd095c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.nda..nda.noShow..22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kha_nyo_nda"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.nda..nda.noShow..22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381682974","data":{"timestamp":" 947381682974"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 5cf1b3e3-e746-4623-a958-00f96dd095c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.nda..nda.noShow..22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_nda_sho_nu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.nda..nda.noShow..22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381689628","data":{"timestamp":" 947381689628"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 5cf1b3e3-e746-4623-a958-00f96dd095c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.nda..nda.noShow..22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_wu_nda_ta"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.nda..nda.noShow..22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381696287","data":{"timestamp":" 947381696286"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 5cf1b3e3-e746-4623-a958-00f96dd095c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.nda..nda.noShow..22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mno_fe_nda"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.nda..nda.noShow..22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381702949","data":{"timestamp":" 947381702949"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 5cf1b3e3-e746-4623-a958-00f96dd095c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.nda..nda.noShow..22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mo_sho_nda"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.nda..nda.noShow..22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381710418","data":{"timestamp":" 947381710416"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 5cf1b3e3-e746-4623-a958-00f96dd095c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.nda..nda.noShow..22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mo_sho_nda"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.nda..nda.noShow..22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381717011","data":{"timestamp":" 947381717010"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 5cf1b3e3-e746-4623-a958-00f96dd095c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.nda..nda.noShow..22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_nda_msta_wa"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.nda..nda.noShow..22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381723674","data":{"timestamp":" 947381723674"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 5cf1b3e3-e746-4623-a958-00f96dd095c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.nda..nda.noShow..22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_nda_bwe_kwa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.nda..nda.noShow..22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381730342","data":{"timestamp":" 947381730342"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 5cf1b3e3-e746-4623-a958-00f96dd095c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.nda..nda.noShow..22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_nda_mba_ndu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.nda..nda.noShow..22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381742458","data":{"timestamp":" 947381742457"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 5cf1b3e3-e746-4623-a958-00f96dd095c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.nda..nda.noShow..22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_nda_mba_ndu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.nda..ndu.asc.lc.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381766534","data":{"timestamp":" 947381766533"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 2ce1b895-04b6-4e80-b10a-47c4eca31fb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nda..ndu.asc.lc.35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDA"," userResponse":" NDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.nda..ndu.asc.lc.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381769117","data":{"timestamp":" 947381769116"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 2ce1b895-04b6-4e80-b10a-47c4eca31fb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nda..ndu.asc.lc.35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDA"," userResponse":" NDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.nda..ndu.asc.lc.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381770716","data":{"timestamp":" 947381770715"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 2ce1b895-04b6-4e80-b10a-47c4eca31fb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nda..ndu.asc.lc.35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nde"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDE"," userResponse":" NDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.nda..ndu.asc.lc.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381778237","data":{"timestamp":" 947381778236"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 2ce1b895-04b6-4e80-b10a-47c4eca31fb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nda..ndu.asc.lc.35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nde"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.nda..ndu.asc.lc.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381779842","data":{"timestamp":" 947381779841"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 2ce1b895-04b6-4e80-b10a-47c4eca31fb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nda..ndu.asc.lc.35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDI"," userResponse":" NDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.nda..ndu.asc.lc.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381782768","data":{"timestamp":" 947381782768"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 2ce1b895-04b6-4e80-b10a-47c4eca31fb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nda..ndu.asc.lc.35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDI"," userResponse":" NDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.nda..ndu.asc.lc.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381784352","data":{"timestamp":" 947381784351"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 2ce1b895-04b6-4e80-b10a-47c4eca31fb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nda..ndu.asc.lc.35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDO"," userResponse":" NDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.nda..ndu.asc.lc.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381786879","data":{"timestamp":" 947381786878"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 2ce1b895-04b6-4e80-b10a-47c4eca31fb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nda..ndu.asc.lc.35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDO"," userResponse":" NDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.nda..ndu.asc.lc.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381788472","data":{"timestamp":" 947381788472"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 2ce1b895-04b6-4e80-b10a-47c4eca31fb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nda..ndu.asc.lc.35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDU"," userResponse":" NDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.nda..ndu.asc.lc.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381791821","data":{"timestamp":" 947381791820"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 2ce1b895-04b6-4e80-b10a-47c4eca31fb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nda..ndu.asc.lc.35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDU"," userResponse":" NDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.nda..ndu.asc.lc.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381793843","data":{"timestamp":" 947381793842"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 2ce1b895-04b6-4e80-b10a-47c4eca31fb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nda..ndu.asc.lc.35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" ndu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381793960","data":{"timestamp":" 947381793960"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 2ce1b895-04b6-4e80-b10a-47c4eca31fb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nda..ndu.asc.lc.35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDU"," userResponse":" NDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.nda..ndu.asc.lc.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381813133","data":{"timestamp":" 947381813133"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 3f6c755e-affb-4cbf-b422-070e3cfd6060"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.nda..ndu.asc.lc.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDA"," userResponse":" NDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.nda..ndu.asc.lc.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381814192","data":{"timestamp":" 947381814191"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 3f6c755e-affb-4cbf-b422-070e3cfd6060"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.nda..ndu.asc.lc.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDA"," userResponse":" NDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.nda..ndu.asc.lc.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381817921","data":{"timestamp":" 947381817920"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 3f6c755e-affb-4cbf-b422-070e3cfd6060"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.nda..ndu.asc.lc.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nde"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDE"," userResponse":" NDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.nda..ndu.asc.lc.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381818985","data":{"timestamp":" 947381818984"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 3f6c755e-affb-4cbf-b422-070e3cfd6060"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.nda..ndu.asc.lc.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nde"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDE"," userResponse":" NDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.nda..ndu.asc.lc.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381825792","data":{"timestamp":" 947381825791"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 3f6c755e-affb-4cbf-b422-070e3cfd6060"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.nda..ndu.asc.lc.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDI"," userResponse":" NDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.nda..ndu.asc.lc.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381826862","data":{"timestamp":" 947381826862"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 3f6c755e-affb-4cbf-b422-070e3cfd6060"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.nda..ndu.asc.lc.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDI"," userResponse":" NDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.nda..ndu.asc.lc.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381831238","data":{"timestamp":" 947381831237"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 3f6c755e-affb-4cbf-b422-070e3cfd6060"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.nda..ndu.asc.lc.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDO"," userResponse":" NDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.nda..ndu.asc.lc.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381832302","data":{"timestamp":" 947381832301"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 3f6c755e-affb-4cbf-b422-070e3cfd6060"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.nda..ndu.asc.lc.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDO"," userResponse":" NDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.nda..ndu.asc.lc.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381835958","data":{"timestamp":" 947381835957"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 3f6c755e-affb-4cbf-b422-070e3cfd6060"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.nda..ndu.asc.lc.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDU"," userResponse":" NDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.nda..ndu.asc.lc.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381837020","data":{"timestamp":" 947381837019"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 3f6c755e-affb-4cbf-b422-070e3cfd6060"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.nda..ndu.asc.lc.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDU"," userResponse":" NDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.nda..ndu.asc.lc.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381840338","data":{"timestamp":" 947381840336"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 3f6c755e-affb-4cbf-b422-070e3cfd6060"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.nda..ndu.asc.lc.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" ndu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381840475","data":{"timestamp":" 947381840475"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 3f6c755e-affb-4cbf-b422-070e3cfd6060"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.nda..ndu.asc.lc.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDU"," userResponse":" NDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381855604","data":{"timestamp":" 947381855603"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" d698cfee-9287-4aa0-aca9-18023383cd47"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mza_mwi-mza-mgu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mza"," userResponse":" mza"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381860149","data":{"timestamp":" 947381860149"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" d698cfee-9287-4aa0-aca9-18023383cd47"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_she_she-vya-nge"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" she"," userResponse":" she"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381865689","data":{"timestamp":" 947381865689"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" d698cfee-9287-4aa0-aca9-18023383cd47"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mba_mto-mba-mti"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mba"," userResponse":" mba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381870479","data":{"timestamp":" 947381870479"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" d698cfee-9287-4aa0-aca9-18023383cd47"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mku_shi-mko-mku"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mku"," userResponse":" mko"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381875916","data":{"timestamp":" 947381875916"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" d698cfee-9287-4aa0-aca9-18023383cd47"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mku_shi-mko-mku"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mku"," userResponse":" mku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381882272","data":{"timestamp":" 947381882272"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" d698cfee-9287-4aa0-aca9-18023383cd47"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mna_mwu-vyo-mna"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mna"," userResponse":" mna"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381886774","data":{"timestamp":" 947381886774"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" d698cfee-9287-4aa0-aca9-18023383cd47"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nje_nje-mgo-vyu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nje"," userResponse":" nje"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381891379","data":{"timestamp":" 947381891379"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" d698cfee-9287-4aa0-aca9-18023383cd47"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nju_she-nju-mjo"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nju"," userResponse":" she"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381899955","data":{"timestamp":" 947381899955"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" d698cfee-9287-4aa0-aca9-18023383cd47"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nju_she-nju-mjo"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nju"," userResponse":" nju"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381905181","data":{"timestamp":" 947381905181"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" d698cfee-9287-4aa0-aca9-18023383cd47"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_cho_mje-cho-mti"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" cho"," userResponse":" cho"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381909871","data":{"timestamp":" 947381909870"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" d698cfee-9287-4aa0-aca9-18023383cd47"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mna_mna-mle-kwa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mna"," userResponse":" mna"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381915541","data":{"timestamp":" 947381915540"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" d698cfee-9287-4aa0-aca9-18023383cd47"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mfa_nde-vye-mfa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mfa"," userResponse":" mfa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381921300","data":{"timestamp":" 947381921299"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" d698cfee-9287-4aa0-aca9-18023383cd47"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_mfa_nde-vye-mfa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381941243","data":{"timestamp":" 947381941243"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" aa8b2d32-1022-47c1-9b36-effa1911c493"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ndu_ndu-chi-nyi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ndu"," userResponse":" ndu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947381945488","data":{"timestamp":" 947381945488"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" aa8b2d32-1022-47c1-9b36-effa1911c493"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mta_nji-mno-mta"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mta"," userResponse":" nji"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382004871","data":{"timestamp":" 947382004871"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" aa8b2d32-1022-47c1-9b36-effa1911c493"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mta_nji-mno-mta"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mta"," userResponse":" mta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382011236","data":{"timestamp":" 947382011236"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" aa8b2d32-1022-47c1-9b36-effa1911c493"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mpi_mpi-bwa-cha"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mpi"," userResponse":" mpi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382017714","data":{"timestamp":" 947382017714"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" aa8b2d32-1022-47c1-9b36-effa1911c493"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mgu_nje-nja-mgu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mgu"," userResponse":" mgu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382044988","data":{"timestamp":" 947382044988"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" aa8b2d32-1022-47c1-9b36-effa1911c493"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nde_kwa-mwi-nde"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nde"," userResponse":" nde"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382052513","data":{"timestamp":" 947382052513"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" aa8b2d32-1022-47c1-9b36-effa1911c493"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nji_bwa-nji-mfa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nji"," userResponse":" nji"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382058787","data":{"timestamp":" 947382058787"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" aa8b2d32-1022-47c1-9b36-effa1911c493"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nja_mwo-vya-nja"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nja"," userResponse":" nja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382067546","data":{"timestamp":" 947382067546"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" aa8b2d32-1022-47c1-9b36-effa1911c493"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mzu_mme-dha-mzu"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mzu"," userResponse":" mzu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382073011","data":{"timestamp":" 947382073011"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" aa8b2d32-1022-47c1-9b36-effa1911c493"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mki_mgo-mke-mki"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mki"," userResponse":" mki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382082648","data":{"timestamp":" 947382082648"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" aa8b2d32-1022-47c1-9b36-effa1911c493"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_thi_njo-swa-thi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" thi"," userResponse":" thi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382088443","data":{"timestamp":" 947382088442"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" aa8b2d32-1022-47c1-9b36-effa1911c493"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_thi_njo-swa-thi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382124151","data":{"timestamp":" 947382124151"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 9dc8453f-6430-402c-aca6-69815f6a1524"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_nji-mko-mme"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382129941","data":{"timestamp":" 947382129941"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 9dc8453f-6430-402c-aca6-69815f6a1524"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_fi-ta-mme"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382135689","data":{"timestamp":" 947382135689"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 9dc8453f-6430-402c-aca6-69815f6a1524"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_mna-mme-no"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382140687","data":{"timestamp":" 947382140687"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 9dc8453f-6430-402c-aca6-69815f6a1524"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_ho-mme-mcho"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382146477","data":{"timestamp":" 947382146477"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 9dc8453f-6430-402c-aca6-69815f6a1524"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_mme-bi-mbi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382152600","data":{"timestamp":" 947382152600"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 9dc8453f-6430-402c-aca6-69815f6a1524"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_sha-mme-ze"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382164795","data":{"timestamp":" 947382164795"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 9dc8453f-6430-402c-aca6-69815f6a1524"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_mwo-mme-vi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382169973","data":{"timestamp":" 947382169973"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 9dc8453f-6430-402c-aca6-69815f6a1524"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_ng'o-ve-mme"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382184836","data":{"timestamp":" 947382184835"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 9dc8453f-6430-402c-aca6-69815f6a1524"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_mna-po-mme"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382201697","data":{"timestamp":" 947382201697"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 9dc8453f-6430-402c-aca6-69815f6a1524"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_sha-cha-mme"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382207490","data":{"timestamp":" 947382207488"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 9dc8453f-6430-402c-aca6-69815f6a1524"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_sha-cha-mme"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382257359","data":{"timestamp":" 947382257359"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" e120ad25-9c14-4b46-8d26-294ac3f0edfd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.68"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_mvu-ve-mme"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382262635","data":{"timestamp":" 947382262635"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" e120ad25-9c14-4b46-8d26-294ac3f0edfd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.68"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_go-mme-sha"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382267657","data":{"timestamp":" 947382267657"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" e120ad25-9c14-4b46-8d26-294ac3f0edfd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.68"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_kwi-mka-mme"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382274143","data":{"timestamp":" 947382274143"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" e120ad25-9c14-4b46-8d26-294ac3f0edfd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.68"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_ng'u-mme-bu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382279632","data":{"timestamp":" 947382279632"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" e120ad25-9c14-4b46-8d26-294ac3f0edfd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.68"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_mcho-vyu-mme"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382286910","data":{"timestamp":" 947382286910"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" e120ad25-9c14-4b46-8d26-294ac3f0edfd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.68"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_mme-nyo-mbo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382294844","data":{"timestamp":" 947382294844"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" e120ad25-9c14-4b46-8d26-294ac3f0edfd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.68"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_ta-ke-mme"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382300334","data":{"timestamp":" 947382300334"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" e120ad25-9c14-4b46-8d26-294ac3f0edfd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.68"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_mme-fa-nji"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382305893","data":{"timestamp":" 947382305892"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" e120ad25-9c14-4b46-8d26-294ac3f0edfd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.68"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_cha-mvu-mme"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382315325","data":{"timestamp":" 947382315325"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" e120ad25-9c14-4b46-8d26-294ac3f0edfd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.68"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_nja-mme-nye"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382321107","data":{"timestamp":" 947382321105"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" e120ad25-9c14-4b46-8d26-294ac3f0edfd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.68"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_nja-mme-nye"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.mme..mme.noShow..23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382351276","data":{"timestamp":" 947382351276"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" a261b01c-d336-4253-ad8b-e00ba1f763e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.mme..mme.noShow..23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_de_mle_mme"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.mme..mme.noShow..23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382357938","data":{"timestamp":" 947382357938"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" a261b01c-d336-4253-ad8b-e00ba1f763e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.mme..mme.noShow..23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ji_mme_mto"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.mme..mme.noShow..23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382364593","data":{"timestamp":" 947382364593"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" a261b01c-d336-4253-ad8b-e00ba1f763e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.mme..mme.noShow..23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_za_re_mme"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.mme..mme.noShow..23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382371239","data":{"timestamp":" 947382371239"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" a261b01c-d336-4253-ad8b-e00ba1f763e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.mme..mme.noShow..23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_cha_mme_mlu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.mme..mme.noShow..23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382377886","data":{"timestamp":" 947382377886"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" a261b01c-d336-4253-ad8b-e00ba1f763e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.mme..mme.noShow..23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_po_mme_mbi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.mme..mme.noShow..23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382384547","data":{"timestamp":" 947382384547"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" a261b01c-d336-4253-ad8b-e00ba1f763e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.mme..mme.noShow..23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_su_tha_mme"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.mme..mme.noShow..23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382391197","data":{"timestamp":" 947382391197"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" a261b01c-d336-4253-ad8b-e00ba1f763e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.mme..mme.noShow..23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mle_mme_mku"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.mme..mme.noShow..23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382397830","data":{"timestamp":" 947382397829"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" a261b01c-d336-4253-ad8b-e00ba1f763e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.mme..mme.noShow..23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mme_mpa_ze"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.mme..mme.noShow..23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382405304","data":{"timestamp":" 947382405304"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" a261b01c-d336-4253-ad8b-e00ba1f763e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.mme..mme.noShow..23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mme_mpa_ze"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.mme..mme.noShow..23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382411980","data":{"timestamp":" 947382411980"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" a261b01c-d336-4253-ad8b-e00ba1f763e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.mme..mme.noShow..23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_le_mme_vyu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.mme..mme.noShow..23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382418623","data":{"timestamp":" 947382418623"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" a261b01c-d336-4253-ad8b-e00ba1f763e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.mme..mme.noShow..23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mme_se_zu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.mme..mme.noShow..23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382430678","data":{"timestamp":" 947382430677"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" a261b01c-d336-4253-ad8b-e00ba1f763e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.mme..mme.noShow..23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_mme_se_zu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382461632","data":{"timestamp":" 947382461631"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 7921a17d-6dc6-4cb3-936b-813918785a47"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMA"," userResponse":" MMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382468372","data":{"timestamp":" 947382468370"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 7921a17d-6dc6-4cb3-936b-813918785a47"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382469955","data":{"timestamp":" 947382469955"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 7921a17d-6dc6-4cb3-936b-813918785a47"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MME"," userResponse":" MME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382474628","data":{"timestamp":" 947382474627"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 7921a17d-6dc6-4cb3-936b-813918785a47"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MME"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382476248","data":{"timestamp":" 947382476248"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 7921a17d-6dc6-4cb3-936b-813918785a47"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMI"," userResponse":" MMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382477207","data":{"timestamp":" 947382477207"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 7921a17d-6dc6-4cb3-936b-813918785a47"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMI"," userResponse":" MMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382478791","data":{"timestamp":" 947382478790"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 7921a17d-6dc6-4cb3-936b-813918785a47"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMU"," userResponse":" MMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382494105","data":{"timestamp":" 947382494105"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 7921a17d-6dc6-4cb3-936b-813918785a47"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mmu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382494209","data":{"timestamp":" 947382494209"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 7921a17d-6dc6-4cb3-936b-813918785a47"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMU"," userResponse":" MMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382544677","data":{"timestamp":" 947382544676"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 7921a17d-6dc6-4cb3-936b-813918785a47"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" mmu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382552161","data":{"timestamp":" 947382552160"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 18dd48c7-bec4-4ff2-923d-74e44d2347ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382590976","data":{"timestamp":" 947382590975"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 18dd48c7-bec4-4ff2-923d-74e44d2347ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382591081","data":{"timestamp":" 947382591081"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 18dd48c7-bec4-4ff2-923d-74e44d2347ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382630112","data":{"timestamp":" 947382630111"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 18dd48c7-bec4-4ff2-923d-74e44d2347ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382656047","data":{"timestamp":" 947382656046"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 79074d0b-06ef-4826-8a67-b69a5edce354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382657136","data":{"timestamp":" 947382657135"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 79074d0b-06ef-4826-8a67-b69a5edce354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMA"," userResponse":" MMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382661075","data":{"timestamp":" 947382661074"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 79074d0b-06ef-4826-8a67-b69a5edce354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MME"," userResponse":" MME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382662136","data":{"timestamp":" 947382662135"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 79074d0b-06ef-4826-8a67-b69a5edce354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MME"," userResponse":" MME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382669027","data":{"timestamp":" 947382669026"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 79074d0b-06ef-4826-8a67-b69a5edce354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMI"," userResponse":" MMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382670118","data":{"timestamp":" 947382670117"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 79074d0b-06ef-4826-8a67-b69a5edce354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMI"," userResponse":" MMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382674023","data":{"timestamp":" 947382674022"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 79074d0b-06ef-4826-8a67-b69a5edce354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMO"," userResponse":" MMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382675101","data":{"timestamp":" 947382675100"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 79074d0b-06ef-4826-8a67-b69a5edce354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMO"," userResponse":" MMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382678817","data":{"timestamp":" 947382678816"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 79074d0b-06ef-4826-8a67-b69a5edce354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMU"," userResponse":" MMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382679878","data":{"timestamp":" 947382679877"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 79074d0b-06ef-4826-8a67-b69a5edce354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMU"," userResponse":" MMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382683608","data":{"timestamp":" 947382683607"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 79074d0b-06ef-4826-8a67-b69a5edce354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" mmu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382683729","data":{"timestamp":" 947382683729"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 79074d0b-06ef-4826-8a67-b69a5edce354"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMU"," userResponse":" MMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382702147","data":{"timestamp":" 947382702146"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 3897d855-45ee-4ec1-ad29-cc4332bed5e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nju_she-nju-mjo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nju"," userResponse":" nju"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382706465","data":{"timestamp":" 947382706465"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 3897d855-45ee-4ec1-ad29-cc4332bed5e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mba_mto-mba-mti"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mba"," userResponse":" mto"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382712300","data":{"timestamp":" 947382712299"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 3897d855-45ee-4ec1-ad29-cc4332bed5e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mba_mto-mba-mti"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mba"," userResponse":" mba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382726444","data":{"timestamp":" 947382726444"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 3897d855-45ee-4ec1-ad29-cc4332bed5e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nje_nje-mgo-vyu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nje"," userResponse":" nje"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382735282","data":{"timestamp":" 947382735281"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 3897d855-45ee-4ec1-ad29-cc4332bed5e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mza_mwi-mza-mgu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mza"," userResponse":" mza"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382760799","data":{"timestamp":" 947382760799"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 3897d855-45ee-4ec1-ad29-cc4332bed5e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mna_mna-mle-kwa"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mna"," userResponse":" mna"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382767299","data":{"timestamp":" 947382767299"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 3897d855-45ee-4ec1-ad29-cc4332bed5e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_cho_mje-cho-mti"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" cho"," userResponse":" cho"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382772234","data":{"timestamp":" 947382772233"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 3897d855-45ee-4ec1-ad29-cc4332bed5e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mku_shi-mko-mku"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mku"," userResponse":" mko"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382777859","data":{"timestamp":" 947382777859"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 3897d855-45ee-4ec1-ad29-cc4332bed5e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mku_shi-mko-mku"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mku"," userResponse":" mku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382784111","data":{"timestamp":" 947382784111"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 3897d855-45ee-4ec1-ad29-cc4332bed5e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mna_mwu-vyo-mna"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mna"," userResponse":" mna"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382790401","data":{"timestamp":" 947382790401"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 3897d855-45ee-4ec1-ad29-cc4332bed5e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_she_she-vya-nge"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" she"," userResponse":" she"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382795744","data":{"timestamp":" 947382795744"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 3897d855-45ee-4ec1-ad29-cc4332bed5e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mfa_nde-vye-mfa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mfa"," userResponse":" mfa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382801535","data":{"timestamp":" 947382801531"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054604"," gameId":" 3897d855-45ee-4ec1-ad29-cc4332bed5e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_mfa_nde-vye-mfa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}